=Deity Of Love= =Episode 11=
= Dewi Cinta = = Episode 11 =
Are sure you are fine?
Apakah kamu benar-benar baik-baik saja?
How about I fetch you a doctor?
Bagaimana kalau aku carikan dokter untukmu?
No need.
Tidak perlu.
I will be alright when I stare at you.
Aku terus mengawasi Nona Qing saja.
- Really? - Sure.
Sungguh?
Well, then lie down and rest.
Ya, kau istirahat dulu.
Does your hand hurt?
Tanganmu sakit tidak?
How about I blow it for you?
Aku bantu kamu tiup, oke?
It is useless whether it hurts or not.
Apa gunanya sakit atau tidak?
Brother won't drink the medicine anyway.
Lagipula Senior tidak akan minum.
The herbs have been boiled or nothing again.
Obatnya dimasak sia-sia lagi.
How could it be in vain?
Kenapa bisa bergadang sia-sia?
It tastes great.
Enak sekali.
Are you stupid?
Kamu bodoh.
Medicines don't taste good.
Untuk apa minum obat?
As long as they are boiled by you,
Asalkan kamu yang memasaknya,
they taste sweet in my heart.
Manis di hatiku.
They are pretending to be husband and wife.
Jelas-jelas mereka berpura-pura menjadi suami istri
Why does Brother treat her so well?
Kenapa Senior begitu baik padanya?
Oh.
Oh, ya.
So it's an impersonation.
Ternyata berpura-pura.
Then I can pursue Miss Xiaoqing again.
Bukankah aku akan mengejar Nona Xiaoqing lagi?
Ah.
Oh, ya.
Miss Xiaoqing.
Nona muda
I'm here.
Aku datang.
This is especially for Miss Xiaoqing.
Ini khusus untuk Nona Xiaoqing
The flowers and jewelry I fetched.
Semua bunga dan perhiasan yang aku temukan
Alas.
Ei...
This one.
Ini...
It's from Spiritual Jade Pavilion.
Berasal dari Paviliun Lingyu.
This is from Frost Flowers Pavilion…
Ini adalah paviliun bunga embun. ..
These all are…
Ini semua. ..
Ouch.
Aduh!
What's wrong with you?
Ada apa denganmu?
No big deal.
Tidak masalah.
It might be some minor injuries.
Mungkin hanya luka kecil.
Back and leg pain.
Pinggangmu pegal dan kakimu sakit.
Let me get you some medicines.
Kalau begitu aku ambilkan obat untukmu.
No need.
Tidak perlu.
Let's go somewhere less crowded.
Kita pergi ke tempat yang lebih sedikit orangnya saja.
Hey, Miss Xiaoqing.
Eh, Nona Qing.
He's pretending to be ill.
Dia pura-pura sakit.
I don't like what you send me.
Yang kamu berikan aku tidak suka.
Such a decisive girl.
Sungguh gadis yang bersih.
My crush on you gets stronger.
Aku semakin menyukaimu.
There is nothing in the world that I can't buy.
Di dunia ini tidak ada yang tidak bisa kubeli.
Miss Xiaoqing, you will be my girl.
Nona Xiaoqing, kamu pasti adalah milikku.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(Hak siar jaringan informasi serial kembali) [Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.] Eksklusif untuk menikmati)